Trust me. No one was there. I didn't see anybody.
A truck just jumped out in front of us, and the car slipped,
and we... I mean I...
I hit the drum in the construction site nearby.
I got out of the car and checked myself.
But we didn't find the drum at the scene of the accident.
I moved it to the side so that no one else would get hurt.
- Please, go check one more time. - I don't need to check.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes.
Yoo Jung said that she was trying to avoid a truck.
That truck driver might be the only witness.
- Find him. And find out what happened on that day. - Yes, sir.
I know Min Hyuk.
The way he looked at her
is love.
- I...- It's okay. Everyone will make a mistake.
It's not a mistake.
Don't you think it's going to be a long night?
That's a deep cut. You should go to the hospital.
Can you stay with me tonight?
No. It's not true.
He was proved to be innocent during the election.
He was there to support a candidate.
It had nothing to do with our foundation.
I have to go.
Have some. We have a lot of things to do.
The building materials sponsored by K Corporation,
I hope we can get it as soon as possible.
Are you really going to marry him?
You told me that we're living in different worlds.
I'm going to marry Min Hyuk in this world.
Min Hyuk knows that as well.
I don't need love.
So you're going to date with me in my world.
You don't like the idea?
Was your heart broken last night?
It it hurs just tell me.
My heart breaks to see you pretending to be okay.
I have a meeting. I have to go.
Mommy. Mommy.
My god.
Mommy! Mommy...
- It's okay. Don't cry. - Mommy! Mommy!
What is this? Look!
Mommy! Mommy!
Where is your mommy?
Say thank you.
You son is so cute.
I can't take my eyes off him for even a second.
You little rascal.
Mommy. Mommy.
Drink it.
You said this gives you energy when you're down.
Don't let me drop it.
It's hot.
Thank you.
Are you going to keep avoiding me?
- The things hapeed that day... - I've already forgotten.
Who ask you to forget it?
I said it wasn't a mistake.
- Sir! - I'm extremely busy at the moment.
But I'm here to see you.
I can't survive without seeing you.
This is the contract from the Hannamdong lady.
You earned it.
Take it to Do Hoon yourself.
- Kwang Soo will drive you there. - Thank you.
It's good to see you like this.
- You have a guest. - Come on in.
Please go through it.
I can't make the decision myself.
You have to wait for the approval of the board.
- You don't want to approve it? - What are you talking about?
Wanting what's not yours is not a good thing.
How dare you say that to me?
Who made me become like this? If you're done, get out.
Why can't I say that?
You're going this far by your own will,
and you're the one who has to pay the price.
Don't act like you're a victim. It's disgusting.
Mr Jo. asked me to take the files tomorrow.
What do you want?
You want compensation?
Compensation?
How can you compensate me?
You took my son away from me and left my father to die in the street.
How much should I get?
I should ask around. What would your parents think?
- Kang Yoo Jung! - Don't say my name!
I'll get that compensation.
You'll pay for what you have done, get ready for that.
- I saw Ms. Kang enter her place. - Good. You can go.
Ms. Kang visited the bakery again after she left Mr. Ahn's office.
Can I ask you something?
Why aren't you giving her back that bakery?
I don't want her to leave.
I'm worried that she might disappear if I give it back to her.
Hello. It's me, Yoo Jung.
I need to ask you a favor.
Hello, sir!
- Take this as collateral. - Sir!
The customer is always right, right?
You should listen to your customer.
Yoo Jung!
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm not supposed to do this.
That's why I'm asking you.
Usually you won't do that.
- It won't cause any trouble, right? - Right.
October 1st. It was in the southbound lane after 11 p.m. and had a Hi-Pass card.
This is the car and the license plate number.
I need information about when the car came back to Seoul.
Yoo Jung, how come Mr. Jo doesn't come these days?
He isn't working here.
Mr. Jo is really sick.
He got an infection around his ankle, and he gets a fever because of it.
- Has he seen a doctor? - His doctor had already checked.
Thank you.
So... What should I do?
I have somthing to do. So...
Don't touch that.
Why are you here?
Are you feeling better?
Aren't you hungry?
I heard you haven't had anything to eat today.
But,
I guess you have nothing wrong with your hands.
If you're done eating, I'm going to go.
That music box
was my mother's.
That music reminds me of her.
I'm not angry at you.
I was scared.
What were you scared of?
My mother died because of me.
If I hadn't gone into that room.
No.
I should never have done this.
I don't want to think about how much my mother would've hated me.
No mother would hate their own child for something like that.
My mother wasn't happy at all in this place.
She'd always look out near the window.
As if she couldn't leave here because of me.
That was it.
There must be a misunderstanding.
Even though I don't know why,
if she really wanted to, she would've left.
It's not that she couldn't leave because of you,
she was able to stay here thanks to you.
If she knew that you were so painful,
she'd be more painful.
I had...
A child.
So...
You can trust me.
Stay!
Can you stay with me for a while?
You're close with Kim Jae Ha recently.
Thanks to Mr. Jo, we've become friends.
I found out who spread the rumor about President Jo.
It was Se Gwang.
You shouldn't do anything suspicious. That's my advice.
Please look at the camera.
Can you turn this way, please?
Don't think you're doing me a favor.
Our target is not only your restaurant.
Stop playing games like this.
Games?
This.
This is what we always do, right?
The press conference is over. Pleas go this way.
Let's go out and talk.
I'm busy. I have to attend my father's election party.
I finished the book, WutHae Ring Heights.
Revenge, which started because of love, ends in tragedy.
Is that it?
I have to go now.
I'm wondering though,
what if things are the other way around.
What happens to love that starts from revenge?
Think about it.
The board permits it and the legal team signed it.
Congratulations!
You can't handel it simply by getting the investment,
Se Gwang still wants King's Restaurant.
Mr. Jo won't give up the restaurant that easily.
I took care of the press.
Things aren't going well, and if this gets out,
no one will trust Jo Min Hyuk's company.
What do you want to say?
This whole thing started because of you.
All the restaurant staff are worried because of you.
Don't pretend that you're caring about them.
You just want to keep your position.
Yes. You're right.
I have a duty to protect the K Corporation.
If Jo Min Hyuk falls, it'll hurt our company.
I'm telling you this because you seem very familiar with him.
Tell Jo Min Hyuk,
He should beg Mr. Kim for forgiveness.
He should say that he did it because of a woman,
It'll be good for both him and the K Corporation.
Hello. Se Yeon.
No, that's okay. I'll be right there.
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry. I'm here to apologize.
Because of me, you and Mr. Jo...
I'll not let it slide because of your apology.
He's such a coward.
He sent you instead?
No, it's not like that.
He doesn't know that I'm here.
I'm the one who should apologize to you.
What do you think you're doing?
It's not in the 80s.
Hey! Get up!
Get up!
Thanks to you, I collected useful information for my company...
But I can't just forgive Min Hyuk for what he did.
He's got a hot fiancee like Se Yeon
and other pretty girls all around him.
How can he be obssessed with a sbustandard product like you?
He sure has a unique taste in girls.
Come on. Pour me a drink.
Whether I'll accept your apology or not depends on your performance.
Driver.
Where have you been?
It's your day off, so you hang out all day long?
Where did you go?
How's your ankle?
Can you walk?
That's good.
I'll go now.
Driver!
Are you okay? Does it hurt?
It's better thanks to you,
but it still hurts.
Isn't Kwang Soo with you?
Why are you here alone?
Kwang Soo is working. Don't worry about him.
Ah.
Right.
Here.
Did you go get the contract?
Nothing happened?
No.
It's getting late. You should go home.
What?
He's recovered.
That's why I said people should obey the law.
They requested to reinvestigate the case,
so they won't let it slide.
We did it to raise funds.
Mr. Choi should explain himself.
I'm not that righteous,
but I'll try my best.
You should be careful, too.
Mr. Choi can tell the judge that he did it because your father made him.
You know he's not that kind of person.
Don't you know that Shina and Se Gwang have their eyes on the K Hotel?
Se Gwang spread the rumor about your father.
Isn't she the one from the hit-and-run case?
What the hell are you doing?
I told you to do what I asked you to do.
Why did you do something I didn't ask?
Well...
Why did you see him?
Why did you pour him a drink?
To apologize.
I heard that your company is in danger
because of what happened that day.
Did Ahn Do Hoon say that?
I thought I did something wrong,
so if I apologized...
Why did you have to apologize?
It wasn't your fault.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have taken you there on that day.
I wanted to apologize.
I wanted to do something to help you.
I can pour him a drink.
I can kneel down.
As long as it helps you, it doesn't matter.
Why do you have to kneel to help me?
It doesn't bother me at all.
It bothers me.
Don't kneel in front of anybody.
I'll kneel myself if I have to.
I have to get back to work.
Let me ask you one thing.
Did you do it for me?
I had no other reason. It just bothered me.
Thinking about you getting in trouble because of me,
it bothers me a lot.
I had no other reason.
Good.
It's been a long time...
Dear!
- I'm okay. - Dad.
- Min Joo! No! - Mom! - I'm good.
Your father is tired.
You didn't miss me?
Did you buy me cosmetics?
- You can only get it from Germany. Did you get it? - Sure. I'll show you.
Let's go.
Gwang Min told me about the investment of western restaurant. You did a good job.
It's just a start.
I need to increase the revenues now.
That's my son.
Are you feeling okay?
I have no intention ofretiring, yet. Don't worry.
You can go. Don't distract from work.
I don't know for sure if it was Ahn Do Hoon.
Se Gwang has so many channels of information.
I don't know where they got it from.
So?
- Excuese me? - When you have something to say, you make that expression.
Go ahead.
Mr. Ahn started as the prosecutor of Seo Ji Hee's hit-and-run case.
- I think Min Hyuk started reinvestigating it. - Why?
It has to do with a girl.
Damn it!
Ms. Kang. We have met before.
Have a seat.
You work at our restaurant?
Yes, Min Hyuk hired her personally.
You helped Min Hyuk get the investment. Thank you.
But I think your work here is done.
You're not going to see Min Hyuk again, right?
Answer him. He's talking to you.
- Well... - Min Hyuk is still not mature enough
to find the right person for himself.
I don't want to see him get hurt again because of a girl.
I thought he learned his lesson.
That's enough. The past is past.
I think she's smart enough to know.
If you're not meant to be with each other, you should let him go.
- We're ready to eat now. - Yes.
- What's going on? - Don't speak that loud in front of your father.
- He's still... - How can you make her sit there?
What are you doing to her?
Let's go!
Kwang Soo!
What are you doing? Let me go! Kwang Soo!
- Mr. Yoon. Get her out of here. - Yes. Madam.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- Sorry. - I told you not to say sorry.
I told you that you didn't do anything wrong.
I'm sorry.
Kang Yoo Jung! Kang Yoo Jung!
Mr. Ahn.
I heard that you know how to handle that girl.
I wanted you to join us for dinner,
but can you deal with her first?
Mr. Ahn.
See? That's the difference between them and us.
I know.
Don't get entangled with Min Hyuk.
What about you? When will you stop entangling with Shin Se Yeon?
Pardon?
Do you think you are qualified to persuade me?
Thank you.
My father's bracelet.
I know that you were registered as my father's contact.
I was wondering if you started from the bracelet.
What a luck.
Don't hurt her.
I'll protect her.
Please don't hurt her.
What are you doing in front of Se Yeon?
I'm okay, sir.
We're going to marry no matter what.
I'll not marry you.
Do you think it's possible?
Seo Ji Hee didn't even have the chance to marry you,
how can the girl who killed Ji Hee become part of your family?
You won't become part of our family, either.
Kwang Soo. Let me go!
Let me go!
I'll not going to marry Se Yeon, I don't need anything.
Se Yeon and I have no obligation to each other.
You...
Sir!
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Min Hyuk, say that again!
Don't hurt her.
Even if it's you, I'll never forgive that.
Let me go!
Get out of my way. Let me go.
Move. I said move! Let me go!
Get out of my way.
I'm worried about you.
Kang Yoo Jung! Kang Yoo Jung!
Yoo Jung! Kang Yoo Jung!
Kang Yoo Jung!
I know you're in there.
Go back!
Thanks god you're here. I was afraid you might have disappeared again.
Please go.
I won't make the same mistake again.
I don't care if my father kicks me out.
Sir.
I need you. I need you beside me.
Stop sying that.
Don't you care about how I feel?
Why should I stay with you after being humiliated by those people?
You don't want to stay with me?
You said you were worried about me.
Yes, I am.
But that's it.
I hate you.
I love Ahn Do Hoon, I feel regret breaking up with him.
I just hate what you have done to me. Please go.
Driver!
Open the door!
Driver! Open the door!
Driver! Driver!
Open up! Open the door!
Yoo Jung!
Please open the door.
Looking at you makes me tired.
I try to forget the accident,
but you keep reminding me of that.
Come out! Let's talk face to face. Come on out!
Please stop!
I knew it.
When it happened... I knew it wasn't just the drum.
I knew about everything.
If I'd been a little more cautious, Ms. Seo Ji Hee
would be with you right now.
I was so happy
and I didn't want to interrupt it.
I convinced myself that nothing had happened.
I couldn't face it, so I avoided it.
I'm the one who killed Seo Ji Hee.
Whenever I see you, I think of that day.
When I see you, the guilt suffocates me.
You really makes me tired.
I really really don't want to see you.
I'll leave.
I'll leave...
Don't be so sad.
Sir!
You didn't do anything wrong.
You always put my father before me.
I found it.
I found the truck that almost hit Ms. Kang's car on the day of the accident.
I'm sorry.
I did a terrible thing. I know it's unforgivable,
but I came here again.
I'm sorry that I'm too greedy.
I know I shouldn't do that.
Just one day.
I wanted to have him for just one day.
I know I don't deserve him.
I know, but I wanted to hold his hand.
I'm sorry.
Next on secret love.
Please let me be with her. I won't marry Se Yeon.
Are you going to be okay?
Isn't it what you want?
What I want is you.
He'll come back when his father falls.
I'll help you.
Mr. Choi will be subpoenaed soon.
I don't know if I should do this.
This happened recently, so it's easier to gather
information than on the hit-and-run case.
I can't end it here.